let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_1.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Atrial Fibrillation",
        options: [
            "First Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Arrest",
            "Second Degree AV Block",
            "Atrial Fibrillation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_2.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Polymorphic Ventricular Tachycardia",
        options: [
            "Atrial Flutter",
            "Monomorphic Ventricular Tachycardia",
            "Polymorphic Ventricular Tachycardia",
            "Ventricular Fibrillation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_3.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Junctional Rhythm",
        options: [
            "Sinus Bradycardia",
            "Junctional Rhythm",
            "Third degree AV Block",
            "Mobitz Type II Block"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_4.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Second Degree AV Block Type II",
        options: [
            "Second Degree AV Block Type II",
            "Second Degree AV Block Type I",
            "Third Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Arrest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_5.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Idioventricular Rhythm",
        options: [
            "Junctional Rhythm",
            "Idioventricular Rhythm",
            "Third Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Bradycardia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_6.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Third Degree AV Block",
        options: [
            "Second Degree AV Block Type II",
            "Second Degree AV Block Type I",
            "Third Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Arrest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_7.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Second Degree AV Block Type I",
        options: [
            "Second Degree AV Block Type II",
            "Second Degree AV Block Type I",
            "Third Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Arrest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_8.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Sinus Arrest",
        options: [
            "Second Degree AV Block Type II",
            "Second Degree AV Block Type I",
            "Third Degree AV Block",
            "Sinus Arrest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_9.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Sinus Pause",
        options: [
            "Sinus Arrest",
            "Sinus Bradycardia",
            "Sinus Pause",
            "Atrial Fibrillation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Identify the Rhythm:",
        img: '<img src="./assets/img/images-gif/question_10.gif" alt="" class="img-gif">',
        answer: "Asystole",
        options: [
            "Ventricular Fibrillation",
            "Asystole",
            "Sinus Arrest",
            "Atrial Fibrillation"
        ]
    }
];